[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "cat",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "horse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "cat",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "cat",
        "falseAnswer": ["duck", "camel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "cat",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "cat",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "crocodile"]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["meerkat", "kangaroo"]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["mouse", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["badger", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "cow",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "cow",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "cow",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "goose"]
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "cow",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "cow",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "sheep",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "camel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "sheep",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "sheep",
        "falseAnswer": ["goose", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "sheep",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "sheep",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["hedgehog", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["turtle", "beaver"]
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["badger", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "kangaroo"]
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "camel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["pig", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["duck", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["zebra", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "horse",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "horse",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "horse",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "camel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "horse",
        "falseAnswer": ["turtle", "goose"]
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "horse",
        "falseAnswer": ["hedgehog", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "donkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "donkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "donkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "donkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "donkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["sheep", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["donkey", "panda"]
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["goat", "antelope"]
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["fox", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["zebra", "jackal"]
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "goose",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "gazelle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "goose",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "goose",
        "falseAnswer": ["hippopotamus", "beaver"]
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "goose",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "goose",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "hedgehog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["llama", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["meerkat", "crocodile"]
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "sheep"]
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "horse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["duck", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "lion",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "rhinoceros"]
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "lion",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "camel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "lion",
        "falseAnswer": ["hedgehog", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "lion",
        "falseAnswer": ["beaver", "gazelle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "lion",
        "falseAnswer": ["squirrel", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "wolf",
        "falseAnswer": ["badger", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "wolf",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "meerkat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "wolf",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "wolf",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "wolf",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "bear",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "bear",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "horse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "bear",
        "falseAnswer": ["jackal", "antelope"]
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "bear",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "bear",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "kangaroo"]
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["dog", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "panda"]
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["zebra", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["turtle", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["badger", "kangaroo"]
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "goose"]
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "donkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["pig", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "beaver"]
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "giraffe",
        "falseAnswer": ["hippopotamus", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "giraffe",
        "falseAnswer": ["meerkat", "panda"]
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "giraffe",
        "falseAnswer": ["pig", "duck"]
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "giraffe",
        "falseAnswer": ["turtle", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "giraffe",
        "falseAnswer": ["mouse", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["pig", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["sheep", "zebra"]
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["donkey", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["meerkat", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["mouse", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "tiger",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "panda"]
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "tiger",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "tiger",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "tiger",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "rhinoceros"]
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "tiger",
        "falseAnswer": ["turtle", "hedgehog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "leopard",
        "falseAnswer": ["beaver", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "leopard",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "leopard",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "leopard",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "leopard",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "pig"]
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "zebra"]
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["fox", "jackal"]
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "crocodile"]
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["meerkat", "kangaroo"]
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["mouse", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["goat", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["dog", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["sheep", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["horse", "panda"]
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["beaver", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "hedgehog",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "hedgehog",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "hedgehog",
        "falseAnswer": ["goose", "antelope"]
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "hedgehog",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "hedgehog",
        "falseAnswer": ["zebra", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "turtle",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "turtle",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "turtle",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "turtle",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "turtle",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "gazelle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "camel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["sheep", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["goat", "antelope"]
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["donkey", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["horse", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "meerkat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["llama", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["squirrel", "beaver"]
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["turtle", "hedgehog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "leopard"]
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "jackal",
        "falseAnswer": ["turtle", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "jackal",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "beaver"]
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "jackal",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "jackal",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "jackal",
        "falseAnswer": ["rabbit", "duck"]
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "llama",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "llama",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "llama",
        "falseAnswer": ["mouse", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "llama",
        "falseAnswer": ["meerkat", "kangaroo"]
    },
    {
        "id": 180,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "llama",
        "falseAnswer": ["snake", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["badger", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 183,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "panda"]
    },
    {
        "id": 184,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["hippopotamus", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 185,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "kangaroo",
        "falseAnswer": ["monkey", "hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
        "id": 187,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "kangaroo",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "antelope"]
    },
    {
        "id": 188,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "kangaroo",
        "falseAnswer": ["pig", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 189,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "kangaroo",
        "falseAnswer": ["camel", "cow"]
    },
    {
        "id": 190,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "kangaroo",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 191,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "meerkat",
        "falseAnswer": ["hedgehog", "rhinoceros"]
    },
    {
        "id": 192,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "meerkat",
        "falseAnswer": ["beaver", "turtle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 193,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "meerkat",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "squirrel"]
    },
    {
        "id": 194,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "meerkat",
        "falseAnswer": ["duck", "badger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 195,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "meerkat",
        "falseAnswer": ["donkey", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 196,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "crocodile",
        "falseAnswer": ["llama", "horse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 197,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "crocodile",
        "falseAnswer": ["sheep", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 198,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "crocodile",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 199,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "crocodile",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "meerkat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 200,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "crocodile",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 201,
        "question": "fish",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["llama", "horse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 202,
        "question": "fish",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["sheep", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 203,
        "question": "fish",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 204,
        "question": "fish",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "meerkat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 205,
        "question": "fish",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "snake"]
    }
]
